

Contact

Phone

+84 77 5854 364

Email

dhthinh7@gmail.com

Address

7 district, Ho Chi Minh City

Website

https://tdprofile.netlify.app

Certification (Download at website)
Front-end foundation developer
Front-end professional ReactJS developer

Education

2015 - 2019 Mechatronics Can Tho University

Thinh Doan

Front-end Dev

Profile

Software Developer in MCAL with over 2.5 years of experience with high responsibility in development, producing quality work. Frontend certified. I'm willing to collaborate with new opportunities and challenges.

Skills

React JS Javascript HTML, CSS, SCSS
Bootstrap Redux Responsive

Verison control: Git, SVN Agile Methodology & SCRUM

Project management: Jira

Projects

Jira clone built with React [1]

A project React cloning with some features simulated from Jira: Users who registered can create, update, delete and communicate together in their project/task.

- Member: 1
- Main role: Responsible for coding frontend, working with API backend, performing responsive on multiple screens
- Technologies: ReactJS, HTML, SCSS, Tailwind, Ant Design, Redux, Redux-Saga

Movie tickets online booking [2]

Decentralization of client/admin site. Booking ticket, and displays the status of booking a seat in real time. Users and list movies list are managed at the admin site.

- Member: 1
- Main role: Responsible for coding frontend, working with API backend, and responsive on multiple screens
- Technologies: ReactJS, HTML, SCSS, Tailwind, Ant Design, Redux, Redux-thunk

WealthCare [3]

Private Wealth Management

- Member: 2
- Main role: Working with API and coding frontend from the design on Figma
- * Note: [1], [2] API from CyberLearn. Visit my website to see the detailed Live demo and source code. [3] This project is on-going

Experiences

11/2021 - 10/2022

Cyberlearn center

03/2020 - 09/2022

Renesas Vietnam

Learning at Cyberlearn center

https://cyberlearn.vn/

Software developer

- Mentoring new member
- Create a tool to save 50% of the time for making reports in the peer review minutes process
- Maintain released devices and implemented new devices from design to testing phase
- Standardized DIT test suite
- Support Renesas Japan to handle IT testing phase